ILR School Audio-Visual Department Video Cassette Collection /4191 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Audio-Visual Department Video Cassette Collection
1955- 2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Audio- Visual Department
/4191 AV
46.67 cubic feet
45.7 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
The ILR School Audio-Visual Department Video Cassette Collection consists of video recordings of various ILR faculty and related people. Some of those included are as follows: Tom Juravich with Labor Songs; Seymour Lipset; an interview with Jimmy Hoffa; J. Sheinkman; ILR Alumni; Sam Bachrach; Lois Gray; George Brooks; Alice Cook; ILR School Anniversary interviews and Jean McKelvey; Milton Konvitz, Maurice Neufeld as well as some conferences and events.
7784786
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 27, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 11, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4191 F: ILR School Audio-Visual Department Films
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Audio-Visual Dept.
7784786
- U.S. Rep Robert Andrews "New Approaches to making Public Policy" - 1/31/1992, 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  MASTER
- Daily News Strike Presentation, 2 (Box 1)
  Juan Gonzalez, NYC Newspaper Guild Strike Leader -- MASTER
- ILR Workplace Conference - 5/24/1990, 3 (Box 1)
- Innovations in Discipline, 4 (Box 1)
  Xerox, Bob Landsman, Tony Costanza (tape 2)
- Innovations in Discipline, 5 (Box 1)
  Jean McKelvey, Snydertank-UAW (tape 3)
- Tom Juravich, Labor Songs, ILR, April 7, 1989, 6 (Box 1)
  J. Amman Prod.
- Presentation by Seymour Lipset at ILR School - 4/25/1991, 7 (Box 1)
  Is America Different? American Exceptional is Reaffirmed -- MASTER
- Presentation by Seymour Lipset, 1991; 8 (Box 1)
  Is America Different? American Exceptional is Reaffirmed -- 4/25/1991 -- Copy
- Interview with Jimmy Hoffa - 4/1975 Conversation, 9 (Box 1)
- UAW Rally Day - 7/30/1987 with UCLEA, 10 (Box 1)
- Interview with Jimmy Hoffa, ILR School - April 1975, 11 (Box 1)
  Duplicate
- Interview with Jimmy Hoffa - 1975, 12 (Box 1)
  Copy
- Promoting the Spirit of Unionism in the 1990s, 1991; 13 (Box 1)
  Bruce Raynor, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, Nov. 7, 1991 -- MASTER
- Promoting the Spirit of Unionism in the 1990s, 1991; 14 (Box 1)
  Bruce Raynor, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, Nov. 7, 1991
- Presentation by J. Sheinkman at ILR School - 4/11/1991, 15 (Box 1)
  The Challenge of the Global Marketplace. MASTER -- Do NOT send OUT
- Presentation by J. Sheinkman at ILR School - 4/11/1991: The Challenge of the Global Marketplace, 15 (Box 1)
  MASTER -- Do NOT send OUT
- Presentation by J. Sheinkman at ILR School - 4/11/1991, 16 (Box 1)
  The Challenge of the Global Marketplace -- Copy
- Presentation by John Sweeney - Pres. SEIU: 2/4/1992, 17 (Box 1)
- Alice Cook, 18 (Box 1)
- The Early Years, 19 (Box 1)
- An Interview with Jimmy Hoffa: 4/1975, 20 (Box 1)
  long version
- An Interview with Jimmy Hoffa - 4/1975, 21 (Box 1)
- Bill Whyte Panel Presentation - 6/5/1994, 22 (Box 1)
- Morton Bahr - 4/12/1993, 23 (Box 1)
- William Bywater, President of IUE, 1991; 24 (Box 1)
  Presentation at ILR conference Center -- 1/29/1991
- ILR Library Expansion, 1 (Box 2)
  Edited MASTER
- Catherwood Library: The Challengethe Opportunity, 1994; 2 (Box 2)
  Edited MASTER --4/1994
- Mellon Foundation Initiative, 3 (Box 2)
- ILR Alumni Report, 1993; 4 (Box 2)
  Edited MASTER -- Spring 1993
- Construction in New York State: a Depressed Industry, 5 (Box 2)
- Catherwood Library: The Challenge, the Opportunity / Advisory Board, 1995; 6 (Box 2)
  Edited MASTER -- 4/1995
- The Early Years of the ILR School, 7 (Box 2)
- Dedication of Robert Doherty Faculty Lounge: June 1989, 8 (Box 2)
- ILR: The Field, the School, 9 (Box 2)
- Employee Ownership: the Emerging Pattern, 10 (Box 2)
- Construction in New York State: A Depressed Industry, 11 (Box 2)
- MILR Grad Student - Recruitment Video, 1991; 1 (Box 3)
  Edited MASTER -- 6/1991
- Ardwyn Binding Products, Small Business Case Study, 1988; 2 (Box 3)
  Edited MASTER -- 10/1988
- Sam Bachrach, Organizational Behavior, 1993; 3 (Box 3)
  Feature Movies Clip Video -- MASTER -- 9/1993
- The Struggle to save Rath Packing: Part I, 1985; 4 (Box 3)
  Edited MASTER -- 7/1985
- The Struggle to Save Rath Packing Part II, 1986; 5 (Box 3)
  Edited MASTER -- 7/1986
- The Original Intent of the Framers, Part II, Prof. Milton Konvitz: 6/9/1989, 6 (Box 3)
- The Original Intent of the Framers, Part I - Prof. Milton Konvitz: 6/9/1989, 7 (Box 3)
- Vicki Saporta - Organizing the Unorganized, 8 (Box 3)
  MASTER Edit
- The Original Intent of the Framers..Does the Supreme Court Really Care? - Prof. Milton Konvitz: 12/8/1989, 9 (Box 3)
- Whyte: 10/18/1980, 1 (Box 4)
- Telstar Communication, Small Business Case Study, 1989; 2 (Box 4)
  New Edited MASTER -- 12/1989
- Whyte - 10/18/1980, 3 (Box 4)
- Whyte Retirement - 10/17/1980, 4 (Box 4)
- President William Foote Whyte - Interview, 5 (Box 4)
- Work in progress, 6 (Box 4)
  Edited version for ILR Freshman Course
- The Early Years, 1 (Box 5)
  Documentary of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
- Lois Gray, 2 (Box 5)
  tape 1 of 1
- George Brooks, 3 (Box 5)
  tape 1 of 2
- Alice Cook, 4 (Box 5)
  tape 2 of 4
- The Early Years, 5 (Box 5)
- Mary Bloejets, 6 (Box 5)
  tape 2 of 2
- Robert Colbert, 7 (Box 5)
- Alice Cook, 8 (Box 5)
  tape 3 of 4
- George Brooks, 9 (Box 5)
- ILR 40th Anniversary Interview: George Brooks, 10 (Box 5)
- ILR 40th Anniversary Interview: Mary Bloejets, 11 (Box 5)
- Prof. A. Cook Interview on 40th Anniversary of ILR School, 1985; 12 (Box 5)
- Prof. A. Cook Interview on 40th Anniversary of ILR School, 1985; 13 (Box 5)
- Vernon "Pete" Jensen, 1 (Box 6)
- M. Neufeld, 2 (Box 6)
  tape 3 of 3
- Milton Konvitz, 3 (Box 6)
  tape 1 of 3
- Vernon "Pete" Jensen, 4 (Box 6)
- Milton Konvitz, 5 (Box 6)
  tape 2 of 3
- Milton Konvitz, 6 (Box 6)
- ILR 40th Anniversary Interview: Lois Gray, 7 (Box 6)
- Jean McKelvey, 8 (Box 6)
- Jean McKelvey, 9 (Box 6)
- Jean McKelvey, 10 (Box 6)
- ILR: the Field, 11 (Box 6)
- Milton Konvitz, 12 (Box 6)
- ILR 40th Anniversary Interview: Gormley Miller, 13 (Box 6)
- Mary Bloejets: ILR 40th Anniversary, 14 (Box 6)
- Never Done: the Working Life of Alice H. Cook, 1993; 1 (Box 7)
- M. Neufeld - ILR 40th Anniversary, 2 (Box 7)
- Effie Riley - ILR 40th Anniversary, 3 (Box 7)
- M. Neufeld - ILR 40th Anniversary, 4 (Box 7)
- Jean McKelvey - ILR 40th Anniversary, 5 (Box 7)
- Jean McKelvey - ILR 40th Anniversary, 6 (Box 7)
- Jean McKelvey - ILR 40th Anniversary, 7 (Box 7)
  Tape 2 of 3
- Bill Whyte - ILR 40th Anniversary, 8 (Box 7)
- Maurice Neufeld, 9 (Box 7)
- ILR Konvitz - 6/9/1989, 10 (Box 7)
- Konvitz - 6/9/1989, 11 (Box 7)
- Maurice Neufeld, 12 (Box 7)
- Maurice Neufeld - ILR 40th Anniversary, 13 (Box 7)
- Maurice Neufeld, 14 (Box 7)
- Effie Riley - ILR 40th Anniversary Interview, 15 (Box 7)
- Never Done: the Working Life of Alice cook: 1993, 16 (Box 7)
- Never Done: the Working Life of Alice H. Cook: 1993, 17 (Box 7)
- Bill Whyte - ILR 40th Anniversary Interview, 18 (Box 7)
- 1990 Holiday Lunch - Pete Nero's Rap, 1 (Box 8)
- 1990 Extension Holiday Party, 2 (Box 8)
- 1990 - Holiday Video, 3 (Box 8)
- Holiday Video - 1989, 4 (Box 8)
- ILR Holiday Lunch - 1989, 5 (Box 8)
- Craft Fair - 1988, 6 (Box 8)
- ILR Extension Holiday Party - 1989, 7 (Box 8)
- Kay Clark Birthday, 8 (Box 8)
- Pat Winder 50th Birthday - 6/29/1993, 9 (Box 8)
- Carol Eastman 50th Birthday - 10/9/1992, 10 (Box 8)
- Gross - Birthday - 6/29/1992, 11 (Box 8)
- Martha Smith Award - 4/7/1988, 12 (Box 8)
- Doherty Lounge Dedication, 13 (Box 8)
- Christmas 1987 w/Dean Dougherty, 14 (Box 8)
- June Niblock Retirement - 9/20/1990, 15 (Box 8)
- P. Strausser Baby Shower - 3/5/1990, 16 (Box 8)
- ILR: 9/1986, 17 (Box 8)
- ILR: 9/1989, 18 (Box 8)
- Johnson Museum - Sue Mason, 1 (Box 9)
- ILR 40th Anniversary Interview: Vernon "Pete" Jensen, 2 (Box 9)
- ILR 40th Anniversary Interview: John McConnel, 3 (Box 9)
- Pete Jensen, 4 (Box 9)
- Pete Jensen, 5 (Box 9)
- Shirley Harper Reception - 2/23/1993, 6 (Box 9)
- B. Weir Pictel - 3/9/1993, 7 (Box 9)
- Steve Johnson Pictel - Govt. Affairs - 3/2/1993, 8 (Box 9)
- Software that Connects People, 9 (Box 9)
- Johnson Grad Pictel - 3/6/1993, 10 (Box 9)
- Street Smart, 11 (Box 9)
- Opening Remarks for Smithers, 12 (Box 9)
- J. Boudreau Pictel - 2/24/1993, 13 (Box 9)
- Martha Eller Pictel - 5/10/1993, 14 (Box 9)
- Depew LFSD vs. Rolls // Pablo/Bob/Jennifer/Christine, 15 (Box 9)
- SEIU Local 200A, 16 (Box 9)
  Panel discussion including Shop Stewards from Jewish Center Nursing Home + Syracuse Univ.
- Congressman A. Houghton - Deficit Deduction, 4/8/1994, 17 (Box 9)
- John McConnel, 18 (Box 9)
- EAP Crucial Balance, Part II, 19 (Box 9)
- The Crucial Balance, Part I, 20 (Box 9)
- Back to Work "Linkages: the Workplace and Treatment/counseling" Part I, 1989; 1 (Box 10)
  Edited MASTER -- 11/1/1989
- EAP D6M Close; E. Clenry - NYS AFL-CIO; Prof. H. Rice - Cornell; M. Savnofro - NYS Div. of ALCO: 1/1990, 2 (Box 10)
- EAP Vignette #4: Mailroom - Peer, 1989; 3 (Box 10)
  Edited MASTER - 11/1989
- EAP Vignette #3: Delco Peer Good, 1989; 4 (Box 10)
  Edited MASTER -- 11/27/1989
- EAP Vignette #2: Delco Bad Intervention, 1989; 5 (Box 10)
  Edited MASTER -- 11/1989
- EAP White Collar Intervention - 10/1990, 6 (Box 10)
  1st Edit -- MASTER
- EAP Supervisor - Committeeman Intervention: 10/1990, 7 (Box 10)
  1st Edit - MASSTER
- A Movement Called Compassion (Trice Lecture), 1989; 8 (Box 10)
  Edited MASTER --1/1989; Re-Edit -- 3/1989
- EAP Sonnenstuhl; Job Performance: 7/1989, 9 (Box 10)
- EAP Closing Comments - 11/1989, 10 (Box 10)
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 1: Morning Session", 1 (Box 11)
  #1
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 1: Luncheon", 2 (Box 11)
  #2
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 1: Afternoon Session", 3 (Box 11)
  #3
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day: Evening Session", 4 (Box 11)
  #4
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 2: Morning Session Part 1", 5 (Box 11)
  #5
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 2: Morning Session Part 2", 6 (Box 11)
  #6
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 2: Afternoon Session", 7 (Box 11)
  #7
- Cornell ILR Human Rights Conference "Day 2: Evening Session", 8 (Box 11)
  #8
- UAW Local 1097: High School Labor Studies, 9 (Box 11)
- UPIU - International Paper on Campus? No Way!, 10 (Box 11)
- A message for AFSCME Families, 11 (Box 11)
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Alumni Report, Spring 1993, 12 (Box 11)
- The Negotiator, 13 (Box 11)
- The Early Years: Documentary of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 14 (Box 11)
- Lois, NYC / Rawlings, Albany, 15 (Box 11)
- The Original Intent of the Framer, Does the Supreme Court Really Care? Prof. Milton Konvitz, 16 (Box 11)
- Feel the Power, the Occupation of the PC World, 17 (Box 11)
- This Ain't Going Away, 18 (Box 11)
- Mobilizing for the New Millennium, 19 (Box 11)
- A Line in the Sand / CAW, 20 (Box 11)
- Reunion 1996 - Former Deans; Picnic 1996, Lipsky Roast, 21 (Box 11)
- JCI Can Fab Occupation: A Fight to Save Canadian Jobs, 22 (Box 11)
- Bob Reich - 4/16/1973, 23 (Box 11)
- Labor Day, 24 (Box 11)
- Labor Day, 25 (Box 11)
- EAP Vignette #5: Union Steward/Supervisor, 1989; 20 (Box 12)
- EAP - Back to Work: Linkages: the Workplace and Treatment/Counseling, Part II, 1989; 21 (Box 12)
- IWO Fratenism in action, 22 (Box 12)
- Cases in Discipline and Discharge, 23 (Box 12)
- New York State Business Report; Comparable Worth / Michael Gold, 24 (Box 12)
- Cases in Discipline and Discharge, 25 (Box 12)
- Comparable Worth / Prof. Michael Gold, 26 (Box 12)
- Arbitration in Action, 1 (Box 13)
- Arbitration in Action, 2 (Box 13)
- Blue Collar Capitalism, 3 (Box 13)
- But it we work together, 4 (Box 13)
- Countdown to a contract, 5 (Box 13)
- Countdown to a contract, 6 (Box 13)
- Asbestos: Fighting a killer, 7 (Box 13)
- An American Valley, 8 (Box 13)
- Ardwyn Binding: Case Study, 9 (Box 13)
- Call the Mediator, 10 (Box 13)
- Delegation w/Prof. S. Rynes - Parts I II, 1 (Box 14)
- Drug Screening on the Job, 2 (Box 14)
- The Grievance, 3 (Box 14)
- Fact Finding Hearing, 4 (Box 14)
- Great Wierton Steel, 5 (Box 14)
- Harmonics of Conflict, 6 (Box 14)
- Grievance Handling, 7 (Box 14)
- It's a Living, 8 (Box 14)
- Whyte Impact on an Underdog; Ralph Orlandella 150 in trade, 9 (Box 14)
- International Metal Workers Federation, 10 (Box 14)
- KOJI: the Mechanic, 1 (Box 15)
- One of those people, 2 (Box 15)
- Job Discrimination (Part I), 3 (Box 15)
- Job Interview, 4 (Box 15)
- John L. Lewis, 5 (Box 15)
- Issues in Arbitrability, 6 (Box 15)
- Issues in Arbitrability, 7 (Box 15)
- Issues in Seniority, 8 (Box 15)
- Issues in Seniority, 9 (Box 15)
- OER Project, 1 (Box 16)
- So Can You, 2 (Box 16)
  OER Human Resource Development Program Modules 5-8
- Perfectly Normal Day, 3 (Box 16)
- New York State Human Resources Development Program, Governor's Office of Employee Relations, 4 (Box 16)
- Pauline Newman Interview, 5 (Box 16)
- Neweott - 9/10/1985, 6 (Box 16)
- Palace Cars Paradise, 7 (Box 16)
- New York is too Good to Lose, 8 (Box 16)
- Moving Mountains, 9 (Box 16)
- Problems at the Start of a Hearing, 1 (Box 17)
- Ready or Not #7 - Employment (Part I), 2 (Box 17)
- Problems in Evidence, 3 (Box 17)
- Problems in Evidence, 4 (Box 17)
- Perfectly Normal Day, 5 (Box 17)
- Performance Appraisal: the Human Dynamics, 6 (Box 17)
- Reflections: George Meany, 7 (Box 17)
- Problems at Start of a Hearing, 8 (Box 17)
- Problems in Mediation, 9 (Box 17)
- Problems in Mediation, 10 (Box 17)
- Solidarity Day 1981, 2 (Box 18)
- Scenes from the workplace, 3 (Box 18)
- Testimony, 4 (Box 18)
- Vicki Saporta (Organizing the Unorganized), 5 (Box 18)
- A Turn for the Best, 6 (Box 18)
- Givebacks: UAW and the Auto Industry, 7 (Box 18)
- Solidarity (UAW), 8 (Box 18)
- Strength Through Struggle, 9 (Box 18)
- Working Women, 1 (Box 19)
  P6M319--P6M326
- You and E.R.I.S.A., 2 (Box 19)
- Working Smarter, 3 (Box 19)
- Working Steel, 4 (Box 19)
- Working Smarter, 5 (Box 19)
- A Yen for Harmony, 6 (Box 19)
- Working without Unions: the Health Care Story, 7 (Box 19)
- Working on Working, 8 (Box 19)
- Who's in Charge, 9 (Box 19)
- What You Are is Not Necessarily What You Will Be - Massey, 10 (Box 19)
- Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies - At Work in the New Economy, 1 (Box 20)
- Battle For Eastern, 2 (Box 20)
- The Bottom Line, 3 (Box 20)
- Buffalo P.E.R.B. Hearing, 4 (Box 20)
- Assault on Affirmative Action, 5 (Box 20)
- America Works - Asbestos School Safety, 6 (Box 20)
- America Works - America's Competitive Edge, 7 (Box 20)
- LEP171V - Enterprise II: Buy Out, 8 (Box 20)
- America Works - Show 206 Child Care, 9 (Box 20)
- America Works: Pay Equity II, 1 (Box 21)
- A Walk Through the 20th Century with Bill Moyers - Out of the Depths - The Miners Story, 2 (Box 21)
- Older Americans in the Workplace, 3 (Box 21)
- America Works / Show 1007C: Prescription Drugs, 4 (Box 21)
- America Works / Show 1001C: Plant Closings, 5 (Box 21)
- America Works / Show 1013: Pay Equity II, 6 (Box 21)
- Prize Is Right, the Job Game, 7 (Box 21)
- Managing Health Benefit Costs, 8 (Box 21)
- A Matter of Judgment, 9 (Box 21)
- The Helping Hand, 1 (Box 22)
- Life of the Western Coal Miner (1), 2 (Box 22)
- America Works / Show 1011C: Hospital Cost Containment, 3 (Box 22)
- If Japan CanWhy Can't We? (Part I), 4 (Box 22)
- America Works / Show 1012C: Financing Education, 5 (Box 22)
- America Works / Show 1009C: Gas Decontrol, 6 (Box 22)
- Health Care: Critical Condition, 7 (Box 22)
- America Works / Show 1006C: Job Retraining, 8 (Box 22)
- Joe Hill - McNeil-Lehrer, 9 (Box 22)
- Feldstein Interview, 1 (Box 23)
- Completing Your LM-3, 2 (Box 23)
- Doctor I Want - Hard Choices, 3 (Box 23)
- America Works / Show 204: Family Farms, 4 (Box 23)
- Community Ownership / New York State School of Industrial Relations, 5 (Box 23)
- DEBS / The American People's Historical Society, 6 (Box 23)
- Chrysler/Labor (McNeil-Lehrer), 7 (Box 23)
- Confidential Helpline, 8 (Box 23)
- Robotics (McNeil-Lehrer), 1 (Box 24)
- Waldenville III, 2 (Box 24)
- Waldenville II, 3 (Box 24)
- America Works / Show 202 Teen Jobs/Fair Wages, 4 (Box 24)
- America Works / Show 205 Taxes, 5 (Box 24)
- Social Security (McNeil-Lehrer), 6 (Box 24)
- The Sky's the Limit, 7 (Box 24)
- Sad Days in Steel Town, 8 (Box 24)
- Enterprise III: Room at the Top, 9 (Box 24)
- Frontline: We Are Driven, 1 (Box 25)
- Work worth Doing Part 1, 2 (Box 25)
- Women in Construction, 3 (Box 25)
- Work, Work, Work, 4 (Box 25)
- When a Factory Closes, 5 (Box 25)
- Waldenville Jogger, 6 (Box 25)
- Work Worth Doing Pt. 2, 7 (Box 25)
- Woman Alive, 8 (Box 25)
- The Leadership Alliance, 9 (Box 25)
- 1989 Case Study for Renovation (Library), 1 (Box 26)
- ILR Library Expansion, 2 (Box 26)
- Unmarked, 3 (Box 26)
- ILR Library Expansion - Produced 1/1986, 4 (Box 26)
- Alice Cook Conference 11/21 22/2003, 5 (Box 26)
- Bob Stern Memorial Service, 6 (Box 26)
- A movement called compassion (by EAP), 7 (Box 26)
- Trade Union Women's Studies (Part I), 8 (Box 26)
- Trumka, Richard: "Direction of American Labor Movement in 1990's", 9 (Box 26)
- The Best Move I Could Have Made for My Career, 10 (Box 26)
- ILR: The Field, the School, 11 (Box 26)
- Cornell 1991, 12 (Box 26)
- Cornell 1991, 13 (Box 26)
- Cornell in 1987: "VDT's in the Workplace", 14 (Box 26)
  part I-Health Concern; part 2-Strategies
- Close Ties: You, Cornell, and the Planned Giving Advantage, 15 (Box 26)
  Media Services, Cornell
- Cornell 1988, 16 (Box 26)
- The Best Move I Could Have Made for My Career, 17 (Box 26)
- Cornell Campus 1975 [Don Milici, Ithaca, NY], 1 (Box 27)
  34 slides
- Cornell Campus - Aerial Views included - 1975, 2 (Box 27)
- Risley/Milkovich; John Gentry - for undsoc. Labor; Juanita Kreps, 3 (Box 27)
- Panel on comparable worth - Alice Cook: Wednesday May 6th, 4 (Box 27)
- Weinberg Seminar 1980, 5 (Box 27)
- Lowi - 11/16/1980: Weinberg Seminar, 6 (Box 27)
- Play with Audio Selector Set to "Both" or "Mix", 7 (Box 27)
- Demo - 1 Gary Fields; 2 Ralph Orlandella; 3 Theodore Lowi, 8 (Box 27)
- Introduction - Dean Rehmus; Risley - Survey Results; Milkovich - New Issues, 9 (Box 27)
- FIS 200 Fall 1988 Final Presentation "Balancing Work and Families: Perspectives of Cornell Employees", 1 (Box 28)
- ILR-Ives Hall Construction, 8/1995, 2 (Box 28)
- Alice Cook: Stories from my life, 3 (Box 28)
- Alice Cook: Stories from my life, 1993; 4 (Box 28)
  MASTER -- 4/16/1993
- COLA CSAS Sweatshop Workers Speak Out! - Feb. 17, 2006, 5 (Box 28)
- Lecture Reading - Cornell - 10/6/1987: Victoria Byerly Katie Cannon -- Hard Times Cotton Mill Girls, 6 (Box 28)
- Victoria Byerly and Katie Cannon: Lecture and Reading - Cornell, 10/6/1987 -- Hard Times Cotton Mill Girls, 7 (Box 28)
- Garment Workers Speak Out: COLA/CSAS sponsored -- Feb. 17, 2006, 8 (Box 28)
- Unmarked, 9 (Box 28)
- ILR School, 50th Anniversary: Panel Presentation by Deans Lipsky, McConnel, McKersie, Moore -- July 8, 1994 Pres. Emeritus Rhodes, 10 (Box 28)
- Trade Union Women's Studies (Part I), 20 (Box 28)
- Trade Union Women's Studies (Part II), 21 (Box 28)
- America Works / Show 1002C: Unemployment Services, 22 (Box 28)
- America Works / Show 1005C: Right to know (Chemicals in the Workplace), 23 (Box 28)
- Waldenville I, 24 (Box 28)
- America Works / Show 1004C: voter Registration, 25 (Box 28)
- Cehrei 1995 Slovak Interviews, 1 (Box 29)
- Slovak Interviews - Summer 1995, 2 (Box 29)
- Czech interviews - Summer 1995, 3 (Box 29)
- Final Offer, 4 (Box 29)
- Cehrei Interviews - Summer 1994, 5 (Box 29)
- Cehrei Interviews - Summer 1994, 6 (Box 29)
- I LR Building Dedication Ceremony: 4/17/1998, 7 (Box 29)
- CNN Pinnicle - 10/24/1999: Cathy Nichols, 8 (Box 29)
- I LR Building Dedication Ceremony: 4/17/1998, 9 (Box 29)
- I LR Building Dedication Ceremony: 4/17/1998, 10 (Box 29)
- Donahue-Trumka Debate, 11 (Box 29)
- Iveta fudrandva Milan Felete, 1994; 12 (Box 29)
  Mellon Foundation Interviews - Close up of interview etc. -- Ivo Koubek -- 6/20/1994
- Jirka Kamenicek - 7/22/1994; Snobrova Gabriela: 8/22/1994, 13 (Box 29)
- Jirka Kamenicek - 7/22/1994; Snobrova Gabriela - 8/22/1994, 14 (Box 29)
- Mutual Interest Bargaining: Turning "Face-to-Face", 15 (Box 29)
  Confrontation into "Side-by-Side" problem solving
- Mellon Foundation Interviews - Long Shot of Interviewer and Interviewee, 16 (Box 29)
  Ivo Koubek and John Boudreau
- John Boudreau Narration, 17 (Box 29)
- Slides for initiative video, 18 (Box 29)
- For the love of words; Your future is yours, 19 (Box 29)
- Your future is now - Research Pgrm #3 - Apr. 29, 1972, 20 (Box 29)
- ILR 21 - Prof. Williams, 21 (Box 29)
- Union Days, April 10, 2008, 1 (Box 30)
- Union Days April 10, 2008, 1 (Box 30)
- 3rd Annual Konvitz Lecture, Prof. Charles J. Ogletree, Jr. (Oct.7, 2008), 1 (Box 31)
- 3rd Annual Konvitz Lecture, Prof. Charles J. Ogletree, Jr. (Oct.7, 2008), 1 (Box 31)
- 3rd Annual Konvitz Lecture, Prof. Charles J. Ogletree, Jr. (Oct.7, 2008), 1 (Box 32)
- 3rd Annual Konvitz Lecture, Prof. Charles J. Ogletree, Jr. (Oct.7, 2008), 1 (Box 32)
- The Power of endowment: the Smithers Institute in New York, 1 (Box 33)
- The Power of endowment: the Smithers Institute in New York City, 1 (Box 33)
- N.Y.S. School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Rochester, NY Arbitration Conference, April 13, 1962, 1 (Box 34)
  New Issues in Collective Bargaining -- Morning speakers are: Jean McKelvey (introduction), Ralph Seward, and Saul Wallen
- U.S. Federal Mediation and conciliation Service. Buffalo District Office, 1967; 2 (Box 34)
  Seminars on collective Bargaining 1967
- U.S. Federal Mediation and conciliation Service. Buffalo District Office, 1967; 3 (Box 34)
  Seminars on Collective Bargaining 1967
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Syracuse, NY - Arbitration conference, May 23, 24, 1965, 4 (Box 34)
  Current Issues in Arbitration -- Side 3 ( c) Continuation of question and answer period - a.m.; (d) 1:30 p.m. cullin - Chairman - How to treat Fired Grievance Procedures - Cole, Blustone, Ferster and Straus
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Syracuse, NY Arbitration Conference, May 23, 24, 1965, 5 (Box 34)
  Current Issues in Arbitration -- Side 4 - Continuation of 1:30 P.M. -- how to Great Fired Grievance Procedures -- questions and answers
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Syracuse, NY Arbitration Conference, May 23, 24, 1965, 6 (Box 34)
  Current Issues in Arbitration-- May 23, 1965 - 9:00 p.m. Sunday Evening - Side I -- Informal Discussion, McKelvey, Gensen, Murphy, Simpkins and Seward // Side 2 -- Monday, May 24, 1965 -- (a) Jensen, Feldsman, Karetz and Wallen (b) Beginning of question and answer period
- Cornell Univ. - 11/8/1973, 7 (Box 34)
- George Meany - Speech at 25th Anniversary Dinner in N.Y.C. - 12/11/1970, 8 (Box 34)
- Baynard Rustin - Speech at 25th Anniversary Dinner in N.Y.C. - 12/11/1970, 9 (Box 34)
- Saul Alinsky, 1909-: Problems of the Urban Poor Given at Annabel Taylor Hall -- Oct. 30, 1967, 10 (Box 34)
- Saul Alinsky, 1909-: Problems of the Urban Poor Given at Annabel Taylor Hall -- Oct. 30, 1967, 11 (Box 34)